Are you kidding me?
Joey?
Joey? Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey, Joey!
Joey. Joey. Joey.
Joey, Joey!
Yeah.
Oh. Oh, did I wake you?
Gunther, could I get another cup of coffee?
So, uh, what do you do when you're not working here?
You don't need to fill these silences.
Okay, thanks.
Chandler, that's your fourth cup of coffee.
I'm drinking lots because I'm exhausted because Joey started snoring.
He's in a different room. He's that loud?
Oh, you should hear me.
It's not something to be proud of. Go to a sleep clinic.
I told you, I'm not going to any clinic.
I don't have a problem. You're the one with the problem.
You should go to a "Quit-being
a-baby-and-leave-me-alone" clinic.
They don't have those.
Yeah, they do.
Quit being a baby and leave me alone!
There, you just had your first class.
I used to go out with this guy that was a light sleeper.
And whenever I'd snore, he'd roll me over...
He'd roll me over, and I'd stop snoring.
Next time you snore, I'm rolling you over!
I gotta do what I gotta do. You gotta do what you gotta do.
Oh, the Olympics!
Have you picked a date?
Huh? Oh.
No. Not yet.
I still can not believe you're engaged.
Just because it's happening so fast. Not because you're a loser.
Thanks. Uh, has anyone seen Rach?
Mm, she's upstairs not doing the dishes.
And I'll tell you, I'm not doing them this time.
I don't care if those dishes sit until they're covered...
I'll do them when I get home.
Yeah. Oh, hey.
Um, Emily found this wedding dress in London...
Already?
Yeah, but it didn't fit.
Luckily, there's a store here with one left in her size.
But I'm the groom...
I'll pick it up for you.
Thank you.
She's got you running errands, picking up wedding dresses...
Ha-ha-ha. Wah-pah!
What's "wah-pah"?
You know. Whipped.
Wah-pah!
That's not whipped. Whipped is:
That's what I did.
Wah-pah!
You can't do anything!
Hey, Mon.
I was just doing these dishes. Oh...
Hey.
Hi. Do you, uh, have a minute?
Yeah, I was just about to take a break anyway.
So listen, uh...
...I know you and I haven't had a chance to talk...
...since, uh, Emily and I decided to get married.
And I was just wondering how you were.
If you were getting married, heh, I would feel kind of...
You know?
Yeah, yeah.
It def... Uh, it definitely took me by surprise. But, you know...
...uh, I'm okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I just wanted to check.
Oh, that's sweet. Thank you. Oh, ha, ha.
You're great.
And I know someday this will happen for you too.
You just hang in there.
"Hang in there"?
Oh, no, I didn't mean...
You haven't heard of a serious relationship called "me and Joshua"?
Oh. I thought you had just been on four dates.
I didn't realize that had become anything.
Oh, yeah. Oh, no, it has become.
Yeah. Oh, no, those were four great dates.
Oh. Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, and the connection! I mean, you know.
Emotionally, mentally. You know?
Physically.
Wow. That's incredible.
I know, isn't it?
I'm right there with Joshua. You are right there with Emily.
And it's kind of like it's a tie.
I gotta get back to my dishes.
I gotta get to work.
You know what would make me happy?
Oh, yeah, no, what's that?
If the four of us could all, you know, hang out together.
Emily's coming into town this weekend.
Why don't, uh, we all have dinner Sunday night?
That would be great!
Yeah?
All right. It's a date!
Right. Yeah.
"Hang in there." You hang in there.
Did you say something?
No, just singing.
Oh, my God!
Oh, look at this one!
It's so beautiful.
Yeah. Oof.
About half of these will end up getting divorced.
May I help you ladies?
Yes, um, I'm here to pick up a dress on hold.
What's the name?
Emily Waltham.
Oh, yes, I have it right here.
Would you like to try it on, Miss Waltham?
You're the most beautiful bride I've ever seen.
I am, aren't I?
Miss Waltham?
Yes?
We're closing.
All right.
And could I get my ring back?
All right, buddy. Time to roll over.
No, no! No, no, no, no, no!
You are going to a clinic! You're going to a clinic!
And a pajama store!
Does she use the cups?
Yes, I believe she does.
Does she use the plates? Yes, I believe she does!
Thank you. Heh.
Aw.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you for coming.
Uh, just a second.
No, no! Let me in!
Phoebe?
Yeah?
Can you hold on a minute?
No!
You have to let me in right now!
Are you alone?
Yes!
All right.
This sucks.
I have to stay up all night before I go to the stupid clinic.
I'm so tired.
It's 6:00.
Hi.
Hey.
I hear you and Joshua are going out with Ross and Emily.
And I think... I think that's really cool.
Yeah, I think you're handling that really well.
"Handling it"?
What do you mean? There's nothing to handle.
Maybe I'd have a problem with this if it wasn't for me and Joshua.
They're not gonna get married anyway.
What?
Come on. They rushed into this thing so fast, it's ridiculous!
They'll be engaged for like what? A year?
Somewhere, one of them is gonna realize what they've done...
...and call the thing off.
You'll be dancing at my wedding before you dance at theirs.
You know, I don't dance at weddings.
Why not?
Weddings are a great place to meet women.
When I dance, I look like this.
Hey, man.
Hey.
So, what are you guys doing four weeks from today?
Nothing.
I am...
...free.
Great, because we're getting married in a month.
What?
Yup.
In a month?
Yeah.
You mean 30 days?
From now?
Yeah.
That's great!
Yeah, ha, ha.
Emily always wanted to get married in this place her parents got married...
...but it's gonna be torn down, so...
I know it's crazy, but everything's been so crazy...
...and it just feels right, you know?
Hey, that's the day after I start menstruating!
This isn't mine.
Ahem
Hey, Rachel.
Hi.
What's up?
Oh, heh.
Your voice sounded all squeaky on the phone.
Oh, nothing. I just wanted to see you.
See you and hug you.
Ha, ha. See you, heh.
Great.
Yeah!
You okay?
I'm more than okay. I am really, really happy.
Want to know why?
Do I?
Because I am really happy about us.
I think we are so on the right track.
I think we are working. I think we are clicking.
You know?
Yeah, sure, sure.
We're... We're clicking.
Yeah.
If there was just one little area...
...where I think we need to work on, I would think...
...it's that we're just not crazy enough.
I got to say, I'm not too sure I agree with that.
Well, yeah. You know, yeah, you're right.
I mean, we have our fun. Yeah?
But, uh...
We ju... I mean, like crazy! You know?
Okay. All right.
This is going to sound, you know, a little, um, hasty.
But, uh, just go with me.
What if we got married?
What?
Oh, I know. It's so totally like:
"Whoa, can we do this?" You know? I mean...
But it just feels right. Don't you think? It does.
I mean, it just feels right. Don't you...?
Rachel, um...
...you're...
...a real...
...special lady.
But my divorce isn't final yet...
...and we've been on four dates.
So I'm thinking no...
...but...
...thanks.
You idiot!
Your name, please?
Joey Tribbiani.
Mm-hm. Did you stay up all night in preparation for your study?
Uh, sir?
Yes, he did.
All right. We'll call you in a few minutes.
Check out that girl. She is really hot.
Yeah, she is.
How you doing?
What?
You're coming on to the entire room.
I'm Chandler. Hi.
I'm Marjorie. Hi.
Do you mind if I sit?
No, please.
So, uh, what are you in for?
I talk in my sleep.
What a coincidence. I listen in my sleep.
So why don't you give me your number?
Are you ready? Okay.
Yeah.
I got it! Mine! Aah!
Congratulations!
Thank you! Ha-ha-ha.
Okay, my turn, my turn!
Okay!
Okay, ready?
Okay.
That was a terrible throw!
I won't throw it right to you. That's not real.
Look at me. My big concern is what's real?
Oh, my God.
We're really sad, aren't we?
Yeah, I think we are.
This isn't even my dress.
At least you didn't rent yours from a store called "It's Not Too Late."
I'm changing out of this.
Me too.
In, like, a half an hour?
All right, now throw it straight this time.
Okay.
I'm getting married next!
I hate my regular clothes now.
You know? I look down and I know...
...this isn't gonna be the most special day of my life.
Yeah. I mean, it was kind of fun for a while...
...but didn't you feel kind of silly?
I guess.
Oh, my God!
Oh, you're such a cheater!
Hello, little ones.
Hey.
So is Joey going to stop snoring?
Yep!
And a beautiful woman agreed to go out with me.
Joey wanted to ask her out, but, uh, you know, she picked me.
How'd that happen?
Because I'm cooler.
No, seriously.
She's the kind of girl... Joey was unconscious.
Hey, you guys! What's happening?
Oh, my God.
What is that?
Oh! They gave it to me at the sleep clinic.
And it's going to help me not to snore.
Well, are you asleep right now, Joe?
You don't have to wear it unless you are.
I know I don't have to.
It tastes good.
Plus, you look cool.
Well, I just called Joshua.
Oh, how'd it go?
I did my best to convince him that I'm not...
...some crazy girl who is dying to get married.
And I'm going through a hard time.
What'd he say?
Well, uh, his answering machine was very understanding.
I feel blue. Ugh.
I bet you anything he'll call you again.
Yeah, maybe. But, you know, I don't think I even care.
I don't think he's the one I'm sad about.
I know I said I'm totally okay with Ross getting married.
But as it turns out...
...I don't think I'm handling it all that well.
Yeah, maybe.
And I'm just trying to figure out why.
Any luck?
Well, yeah. You know how Ross and I have always been...
...on-again, off-again, on-again, off-again?
I guess I just figured, somewhere down the road...
...we would be on-again.
Again.
You know what? I think we all did.
Hey.
I got us reservations for Sunday night.
How about Ernie's at 9:00?
Yeah, well, you, uh, better make it for three.
See, I don't know if we're going to be hungry at 3:00.
Three people.
Joshua's not going to be there.
What happened?
Um, well, I think he broke up with me.
No. Why?
Apparently, he scares easy.
Rachel, I'm sorry.
Eh, it's okay.
Sometimes things don't work out the way you thought they would.
Come here.
Oh, hey, don't you have to go pick up Emily?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I got my girls.
Okay.
Hey, you know what might cheer you up?
What?
I got to tell you...
...this really does put me in a better mood.
Ah, I wish there was a job where I could wear this all the time.
Maybe someday there will be.
Oh, God, that's Chandler coming by to borrow candles for his big date.
No, Rachel, don't get it! He'll see us!
No, yeah! The groom cannot see the bride.
I'm not going to marry Chandler.
Not after this!
Okay guys, just relax.
I do!
I gotta go.
Wait, Joshua!
Yeah, well, that ought to do it.
Food's here. Fair enough.
Fifteen-minute warning.
Late.
Dude, I am trying to sleep!